<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WANIX</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WANIX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:10:33 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Two</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/two/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 15:10:33 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/two/</guid>
      <description>Look again at that dot. That&amp;rsquo;s here. That&amp;rsquo;s home. That&amp;rsquo;s us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &amp;ldquo;superstar,&amp;rdquo; every &amp;ldquo;supreme leader,&amp;rdquo; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there&amp;ndash;on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:50:23 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/one/</guid>
      <description>There is no strife, no prejudice, no national conflict in outer space as yet. Its hazards are hostile to us all. Its conquest deserves the best of all mankind, and its opportunity for peaceful cooperation many never come again. But why, some say, the moon? Why choose this as our goal? And they may well ask why climb the highest mountain? Why, 35 years ago, fly the Atlantic? Why does Rice play Texas?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
